[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This woman was the first female licensed physician in Great Britain. She died on December 17, 1917 at the age of 81.", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Garrett Anderson", "incorrect_answers": ["Agnodice", "Dr. Quinn", "Florence Nightingale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Generally computers are sold with RAM in 1GB denominations. Is it generally possible to add RAM to the system later to have 1.5 GB of RAM?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mascarpone is a  vegetarian Italian cheese, traditionally included in the recipe for  what layered dessert?", "correct_answer": "Tiramisu", "incorrect_answers": ["Semlor", "Pepparkakor", "Aebleflaesk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Niacin, also known as vitamin B3, is required for healthy hair.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1997 movie received the Oscar for Best Picture at the 70th Academy Awards ceremony in 1998.", "correct_answer": "Titanic", "incorrect_answers": ["Good Will Hunting", "L.A. Confidential", "As Good as It Gets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Endorphins are some of the so-called hormones of happiness. In what situations does our body choose to start producing endorphins?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["When we feel pain", "When we are dying", "In times of exhilaration"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Brians punishment for graffiting a (mis-spelt) insult to the Romans on the palace in the comedy Monty Pythons Life of Brian?", "correct_answer": "Writing it out properly one hundred times", "incorrect_answers": ["Crucifixion", "Prison", "Stoning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the correct definition of the word rod?", "correct_answer": "A unit of measure equal to 16.5 feet", "incorrect_answers": ["A unit of measure equal to 3 bushels", "A unit of measure equal to 6 feet", "A unit of measure equal to the distance from a persons nose to his/her outstretched arm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "New Guinea is the most linguistically diverse area in the world. Approximately how many separate languages are spoken there?", "correct_answer": "1000", "incorrect_answers": ["80", "20", "650"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is untrue about the star of the 1939 film The Hound of the Baskervilles?", "correct_answer": "He fought with the RAF during World War II.", "incorrect_answers": ["A relative of his was stabbed by John Wilkes Booth when Lincoln was assassinated.", "He was considered the best fencer in the movie industry.", "He was not born in Europe, Canada or the USA ."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ireland, Germany and Austria are famous for the high consumption of this alcohol.", "correct_answer": "Beer", "incorrect_answers": ["Brandy", "Wine", "Vodka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Asteraceae is a flower, commonly known as this.", "correct_answer": "All of the these", "incorrect_answers": ["Daisy", "Black Eyed Susan", "Aster"]}]